maxutils.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy - www.maxutils.com

## Terms of Use:

By visiting our site you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions and privacy policy of maxutils.com. We may change these terms and conditions at any time. Your continued use of maxutils.com means that you accept any new or modified terms and conditions that we come up with. Please re-visit the terms & conditions and privacy policy at our site from time to time to stay abreast of any changes that we may introduce. The term ` maxutils.com' is used through this entire document to refer to the website, its owners and associates of the owner whatsoever may be. 

**Registration**  
By registering at maxutils.com, you certify that you are agree with terms & conditions and privacy policy of "maxutils.com". If you do not login at maxutils.com for a continuous period of 90 days your registration may get automatically cancelled. Maxutils.com reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to deny you access to this website or any portion thereof without notice with immediately effect. ( Please also go through all about our Privacy Policy in this document before Registration ) 

**Liability Disclaimer**  
You expressly agree that use of the website is at your sole risk. The contents, information, software, products, features and services published on this web site may include inaccuracies or typographical errors. Changes are periodically added to the contents herein. Maxutils.com the owner may may make improvements and/or changes in this web site at any time. This web site may be temporarily unavailable from time to time due to required maintenance, telecommunications interruptions, or other disruptions. Maxutils.com (and its owners or any other associated entities, all collectively referred to as associated entities hereafter) shall not be liable to user or member or any third party. Maxutils.com exercise its right to modify or discontinue any or all of the contents, information, software, products, features and services published on this website. 

.com make no representations about the suitability of the contents, information, software, products, features and services contained on this web site for any purpose. ll such contents, information, software, products, features and services are provided "as is" without warranty of any kind. in no event shall maxutils.com and/or its associated entities be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special or consequential damages arising out of or in any way connected with the use of this web site or with the delay or inability to use this website, or for any contents, information, software, products, features and services obtained through this web site, or otherwise arising out of the use of this web site. 

**Information Disclaimer**  
You acknowledge that the information provided through maxutils.com is compiled from sources, which are beyond the control of maxutils.com though such information is recognized by the parties to be generally reliable, the parties acknowledge that inaccuracies may occur and maxutils.com does not warrant the accuracy or suitability of the information. for this reason, as well as the possibility of human and mechanical errors and other factors, you acknowledge that maxutils.com is provided to you on an "as is, with all faults" basis. maxutils.com expressly disclaims any and all warranties, whether express, oral, implied, statutory or otherwise, of any kind to the users and/or any third party, including any implied warranties of accuracy, timeliness, completeness. 

**Ownership / Copy right**  
The information contained in this site is the valuable and nothing in this Agreement shall be construed as transferring or assigning any such ownership rights to you. You agree not to repeat or rebroadcast in any way any of the information made on maxutils.com for any reason whatsoever. You agree that if you do repeat or re-post any of maxutils.com, you will be liable for actual and punitive damages as determined by maxutils.com and additional damages to be determined by a Indian court of Law. 

## Privacy Policy

At www.maxutils.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. We are fully disclosing our privacy policy. We encourage you to read our privacy statement to understand what types of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information. 

**About Registration & For Registered User**  
Only for the purpose of registration and in order to receive auto email from maxutils.com to help you to maintain your signIn activities ( link to activate your account / unlock user / forget password etc. purposes) collects your e-mail address and no other personally identifiable information is collected on registration by maxutils.com Maxutils.com do not ask you to provide Personally Identifiable information viz. first and last name, physical address, phone number, birth date, and any other information that itself identifies or may identify you as a specific individual at the time of registration. 

As this website does not collect personally identifiable information as like defined above (except e-mail address) and in case you knowingly provide any such information at maxutils.com in any field or input area of its customized product / content, or any type of information whatsoever of kind that is required to be kept as confidential viz. passwords, financial transactions etc. in the input fields provided here. The site owner will not be held responsible / liable in any manner whatsoever for any loss or damage caused to the user. 

Maxxutils.com may use your basic information collected on registration i.e. your email address for the purpose to respond to your requests for our customized products and services provided at maxutils.com or conduct of your account or to inform you about the updates of services and contents of the website in in addition to your SingIn activities of system auto generated emails of your action of registration / unlock user / forget password etc. 

Maxutils.com may disclose the information available with maxutils.com, if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the site or its owners; (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of the site-owners, the site or the users of maxutils.com, and (iii) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of maxutils.com, the site, its owners, or the public. 

## For All Site users

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.maxutils.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user?s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Like most other websites, maxutils.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. 

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.maxutils.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.maxutils.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_adsl 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......  
Google Adsense 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.maxutils.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.maxutils.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.maxutils.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
